Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Bambaataa, Afrika hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music Collection
  - 12 inch Vinyl
    - Not annotated
      Series contains vinyl discs that are either not annotated or the annotations are small and were missed during the sorting of discs. While some effort was taken to bring together piences that were dense in copy-specific track preferences. These items are arranged in alphabetical order by artists’ last name or the name of the group. Each letter of the alphabet has a subseries. Compilations, soundtracks, and other albums with various artists are in subseries together. Artists and groups whose names start with a number are in a separate subseries. Most artists are alphabetized under the name they are most well-known as (e.g. Puff Daddy; Prince; Fela). The variations of names are contained in the Creator field. In a few cases, however, artists’ aliases were unknown, and they may have been listed under two different artist names.
      - M
        - M - Moonlight and muzak, 1979; SR-19624; M (Box 343)
          Catalog # PRO-A-842-RE-2; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-842-RE2-S-A1
          Sire
          New York, New York
        - M - That's the way the money goes, 1979; SR-19625; M (Box 343)
          Catalog # PRO-A-851; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-851-A2
        - M-1 - Early; Comrade's call, 2005; SR-19626; M-1 (Box 343)
          Catalog # KOC-12-5859; A-side Matrix # KOC-12-5859-A-2
          Koch Entertainment
        - M-4-Sers - One nation, 1987; SR-19627; M-4-Sers (Box 343)
          Catalog # JR.6010; A-side Matrix # JR-6010-A
          JR Records
          Miami, Florida
        - M-4-Sers - Roll, pump, shake & ride, 1994; SR-19628; M-4-Sers (Box 343)
          Catalog # JR-6034; A-side Matrix # JR-6034-A
        - M-Beat - Incredible, 1994; SR-19629; M-Beat (Box 343)
          Catalog # 697 120 057-1; A-side Matrix # 697-120-057-1 A
          Payday
        - M. Doc - Like 'em like that (guess I'm just a freak); This world is crazy, 1995; SR-19630; M. Doc; Stevio (Box 343)
          Catalog # IDS 1002; A-side Matrix # IDS-1002-A
          Indasoul Records
          Chicago, Illinois
        - Masters of Ceremony - Crime, 1985; SR-19631; Masters of Ceremony (Box 343)
          Catalog # AB 10959; A-side Matrix # 10-9-59-A
          M-Low Records
        - M People - One night in heaven, 1994; SR-19632; M People (Box 343)
          Catalog # 49 77613; A-side Matrix # XSS-77613-A-1A
          Epic Dance
        - M-Zee Band - Doctor rhythm, 1981; SR-19633; M-Zee Band (Box 343)
          Catalog # DMD 282; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-40188-2
          Mirage
        - M-Zee Band - Doctor rhythm, 1981; SR-19634; M-Zee Band (Box 343)
          Catalog # WTG 19309; A-side Matrix # ST-WTG-814739-C
        - M-Zee Band - Who's funkin' you; Sure shot, 1981; SR-19635; M-Zee Band (Box 343)
          In same jacket as # SR-19636. 2 copies.
          Catalog # DMD 297; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-40187-Z
        - M-Zee Band - Who's funkin' you; Sure shot, 1981; SR-19636; M-Zee Band (Box 343)
          In same jacket as # SR-19635. 2 copies.
        - M + M - Cooling the medium, 1984; SR-19637; M + M (Box 343)
          Catalog # JW-13920; A-side Matrix # PW-13920-A-1
          RCA
        - M3 - Givittame, 1995; SR-19638; M3 (Box 343)
          Catalog # RT0001LP; A-side Matrix # RT-0001-A
          Rooftop Records
        - Maal, Baaba - Wango, 1994; SR-19639; Maal, Baaba (Box 343)
          Catalog # 387471; A-side Matrix # 38747-1-A
          Syllart Records
          Paris, France
        - Maal, Baaba - Wango, 1994; SR-19640; Maal, Baaba (Box 343)
        - Maal, Baaba - Baayo, 1991; SR-19641; Maal, Baaba (Box 343)
          Catalog # 162-539 907-1; A-side Matrix # 162 539 907-1A RE-3 SP
          Mango
        - Maal, Baaba - Baayo, 1991; SR-19642; Maal, Baaba (Box 343)
        - Mabuse, Sipho - Burn out, 1987; SR-19643; Mabuse, Sipho (Box 343)
          Catalog # 009816; A-side Matrix # 9816 A 21
          Virgin
        - Mac & A.K. - Westbound (for riders only), 1996; SR-19644; Mac & A.K. (Box 343)
          Catalog # SL 1148; A-side Matrix # TB 1148-A
          Street Life Entertainment
          Menlo Park, California
        - Mac Band - Roses are red, 1980; SR-19645; Mac Band; McCampbell Brothers (Box 343)
          Catalog # MCA-23791; A-side Matrix # MCA-718-HV2
          MCA Records
          Universal City, California
        - MacDonald, Ralph - Sound of a drum, 1976; SR-19646; MacDonald, Ralph (Box 343)
          Catalog # MARLIN 2202; A-side Matrix # MARLON-2202-A
          Marlin
          Hialeah, Florida
        - MacDonald, Ralph - The path, 1978; SR-19647; MacDonald, Ralph (Box 343)
          Catalog # MARLIN 2210; A-side Matrix # MAR-2210-A-DJ
        - Mac, Elli - Celebrate (the remixes), 1996; SR-19648; Mac, Elli (Box 343)
          Catalog # MM 88431-1; A-side Matrix # MM88431-1 A S-34058
          Moonshine Music
          Los Angeles, California
        - Mac Vo - Players only; Never trust a hoe, 1995; SR-19649; Mac Vo (Box 343)
          Catalog # RPROLP0382; A-side Matrix # RPROLP-0382A
          Relativity
        - Macaluso, Mike - Tribal mayhem, 2000; SR-19650; Macaluso, Mike (Box 343)
          Catalog # ND 20429; A-side Matrix # ND-20429-A
          Nervous Dog Records
        - Mach 1 - Roadrunner, 1997; SR-19651; Mach 1 (Box 343)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # DOS 042-H1
          Dos or Die Records
          Germany
        - Machel - Come dig it, 1995; SR-19652; Machel (Box 343)
          In same jacket as # SR-19653. 2 copies.
          Catalog # PY 7243 8 58488 1 0; A-side Matrix # Y-1-58488-Z1
          Delicious Vinyl
        - Machel - Come dig it, 1995; SR-19653; Machel (Box 343)
          In same jacket as # SR-19652. 2 copies.
        - Machinations - Pressure sway, 1983; SR-19654; Machinations (Box 343)
          Catalog # SP-12077; A-side Matrix # AM SP 012077-A ES1
          A&M Records
          Santa Monica, California
        - Machinations - No say in it; 5 minutes black, 1986; SR-19655; Machinations (Box 343)
          Catalog # EAS 2348; A-side Matrix # XSS-175114-1A
          Epic
        - Machine - Machine, 1979; SR-19656; Machine (Box 343)
          Catalog # AFL1-3410; A-side Matrix # AFL1-3410A-15
          RCA Victor
        - Machine - Moving on, 1980; SR-19657; Machine (Box 343)
          Catalog # AFL1-3529; A-side Matrix # AFL1-3529-A-2
        - Machine Orchestra - Survival, 1992; SR-19658; Machine Orchestra (Box 343)
          Catalog # 162-530 612-1; A-side Matrix # 162-530-612-10-AS SP
          Great Jones
        - Mack 10 - Only in California, 1997; SR-19659; Mack 10 (Box 343)
          Catalog # SPRO 30217; A-side Matrix # S-36693
          Priority Records
        - Mack 10 - Only in California, 1997; SR-19660; Mack 10 (Box 343)
          In same jacket as # SR-19661. 2 copies.
        - Mack 10 - Only in California, 1997; SR-19661; Mack 10 (Box 343)
          In same jacket as # SR-19660. 2 copies.
        - Mack 10 - Let the games begin, 1999; SR-19662; Mack 10 (Box 343)
          Catalog # SPRO 81195; A-side Matrix # S-40837
        - Mack 10 - Backyard boogie, 1997; SR-19663; Mack 10 (Box 343)
          Catalog # SPRO 30153; A-side Matrix # S-35830
        - Mack 10 - Nothin' but the cavi hit, 1996; SR-19664; Mack 10; Tha Dogg Pound; Master P (Box 343)
          In same jacket as # SR-19665. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SPRO 30102; A-side Matrix # SPRO-30102-A
        - Mack 10 - Nothin' but the cavi hit, 1996; SR-19665; Mack 10; Tha Dogg Pound; Master P (Box 343)
          In same jacket as # SR-19664. 2 copies.
        - Mack 10 - On them thangs, 1995; SR-19666; Mack 10 (Box 343)
          Catalog # SPRO 50902; A-side Matrix # S-31644
        - Mack 10 - From tha streetz, 2000; SR-19667; Mack 10 (Box 343)
          Catalog # SPRO 81367; A-side Matrix # S-43732
        - Mack 10 - Foe life, 1995; SR-19668; Mack 10 (Box 343)
          In same jacket as # SR-19669. 2 copies.
          Catalog # SPRO 50877; A-side Matrix # SPRO-50877-A
        - Mack 10 - Foe life, 1995; SR-19669; Mack 10 (Box 343)
          In same jacket as # SR-19668. 2 copies.
        - Mack 10 - Foe life, 1995; SR-19670; Mack 10 (Box 343)
          In same jacket as # SR-19671. 2 copies.
        - Mack 10 - Foe life, 1995; SR-19671; Mack 10 (Box 343)
          In same jacket as # SR-19670. 2 copies.
        - Mack 10 - Westside slaughterhouse, 1995; SR-19672; Mack 10 (Box 343)
          Catalog # SPRO 30027; A-side Matrix # SPRO 30027 A
        - Mack, Craig - Flava in ya ear, 1994; SR-19673; Mack, Craig (Box 343)
          In same jacket as # SR-19674. Different discs.
          Catalog # BBDP-9003; A-side Matrix # BBDP-9003-SA-SP2-DMM
          Bad Boy Entertainment
        - Mack, Craig - Get down, 1994; SR-19674; Mack, Craig (Box 343)
          In same jacket as # SR-19673. Different discs.
          Catalog # 78612-79013-1; A-side Matrix # 78612-79013-1 SA1-RE1
        - Mack, Craig - Flava in ya ear, 1994; SR-19675; Mack, Craig (Box 343)
        - Mack da Maniak - What goes up, 1995; SR-19676; Mack da Maniak (Box 343)
          Catalog # 25040-1; A-side Matrix # 25040-1-A-RE1
          Select Records
        - Mack, Jimmie - Jimmie Mack and the jumpers, 1980; SR-19677; Mack, Jimmie (Box 343)
          Catalog # AFL1-3698; A-side Matrix # AFLI-3698-A1
        - Mack Machine - Count on me, 1994; SR-19678; Mack Machine; B'ernod, Karen (Box 343)
          Catalog # 162-440 601-1; A-side Matrix # 162-440-601-1-AS/HS
          G-Zone
        - Mack Machine - Gotta be free, 1994; SR-19679; Mack Machine; B'ernod, Karen (Box 343)
          Catalog # 162-440 605-1; A-side Matrix # 162-440-605-1 A
        - Mackintosh, C.J. - The tables are turnin', 1987; SR-19680; Mackintosh, C.J.; Einstein (Box 344)
          Catalog # NOTE 4; A-side Matrix # NOTE-4-A*
          Music of Life
          Denmark
        - M.A.D. - Prison or streets, 1996; SR-19681; M.A.D. (Box 344)
          Catalog # SS13096; A-side Matrix # SS-13096-A
          Striktly Records
          Clifton, New Jersey
        - Mad Cobra - Dancehall sampler, 1996; SR-19682; Mad Cobra (Box 344)
          Catalog # SPRO-11623; A-side Matrix # SPRO-11623 A
          EMI Records
        - Mad Cobra - Hard to wet, easy to dry, 1992; SR-19683; Mad Cobra (Box 344)
          Catalog # C 52751; A-side Matrix # 52751-AL
          Columbia
        - Mad Cobra - Big long john, 1996; SR-19684; Mad Cobra (Box 344)
          Catalog # SPRO-10496; A-side Matrix # SPRO-10496-A
        - Mad Doctor X - Dr. X's hip hop experiments escape from the lab and go on the rampage Vol. 1, 1996; SR-19685; Mad Doctor X (Box 344)
          Catalog # FUNKR 005; A-side Matrix # FUNKR005 A1
          Blapps! Records
          United Kingdom
        - Mad Dog Clique - Bump'n in your trunk, 1997; SR-19686; Mad Dog Clique (Box 344)
          Catalog # CTR-1021; A-side Matrix # L-48866
          Crosstown Records
          Cincinnati, Ohio
        - Mad Doctor X - Real heavy science, 1997; SR-19687; Mad Doctor X (Box 344)
          Catalog # FNT6; A-side Matrix # FNT-6-A1
          Freskanova
        - Mad Drama - Ain't no room; Nod ya head, 1995; SR-19688; Mad Drama (Box 344)
          Catalog # 73008-24112-1; A-side Matrix # 73008-24112-1-A
          LaFace Records
          Atlanta, Georgia
        - Mad Flava - From the ground unda (disc one), 1994; SR-19689; Mad Flava (Box 344)
          In same jacket as # SR-19690. Double album.
          Catalog # P1 57199; A-side Matrix # P1-57199-A
        - Mad Flava - From the ground unda (disc two), 1994; SR-19690; Mad Flava (Box 344)
          In same jacket as # SR-19689. Double album.
          Catalog # P1 57199; A-side Matrix # P1-57199-C
        - Mad-Hatter - Dracula's boogie, 1984; SR-19691; Mad-Hatter (Box 344)
          Catalog # T.R.601; A-side Matrix # TR-601-A
          Thrill Records
        - Mad House Loonatiks - Boricuas comming action, 1994; SR-19692; Mad House Loonatiks (Box 344)
          In same jacket as # SR-19693. 2 copies.
          Catalog # FR-001; A-side Matrix # BM-REC-RDS-A
          BM Records
          Puerto Rico
        - Mad House Loonatiks - Boricuas comming action, 1994; SR-19693; Mad House Loonatiks (Box 344)
          In same jacket as # SR-19692. 2 copies.
        - Mad House Loonatiks - Boricuas comming action, 1994; SR-19694; Mad House Loonatiks (Box 344)
          In same jacket as # SR-19695. 2 copies.
        - Mad House Loonatiks - Boricuas comming action, 1994; SR-19695; Mad House Loonatiks (Box 344)
          In same jacket as # SR-19694. 2 copies.
        - Mad Kap - Look ma duke, no hands, 1993; SR-19696; Mad Kap (Box 344)
          Catalog # 07863-66161-1; A-side Matrix # 07863-66161-1-A-ZS
        - Mad Lion - Weed is all we need; Self help, 2000; SR-19697; Mad Lion (Box 344)
          Catalog # PRO-A-100333; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-100333-A-SR1
          Warrior Wax
          United States
        - Mad Lion - Bring it if you want it; Platinumize, 2000; SR-19698; Mad Lion (Box 344)
          Catalog # PRO-A-100163; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-100163-A-SR1
        - M.A.D. - Love, 1998; SR-19699; M.A.D. (Box 344)
          Catalog # CF2837; A-side Matrix # CF-2837 A
          Caffeine Records
          Massapequa Park, New York
        - Mad Moses - Panther party (disc one), 1997; SR-19700; Mad Moses (Box 344)
          In same jacket as # SR-19701. Double album.
          Catalog # MOSES 1; A-side Matrix # MOSES 1 A PROMO
          Hi Life Recordings
          London, United Kingdom
        - Mad Moses - Panther party (disc two), 1997; SR-19701; Mad Moses (Box 344)
          In same jacket as # SR-19700. Double album.
          Catalog # MOSES 2; A-side Matrix # MOSES 2 C PROMO
        - Mad Racket - Supa; Don don da, 1991; SR-19702; Mad Racket; Dope, Kenny (Box 344)
          Catalog # 0-85276; A-side Matrix # 0-85276-A
          Atlantic
        - Madagascar - Spirit of the street, 1981; SR-19703; Madagascar (Box 344)
          Catalog # AL 9565; A-side Matrix # AL9565-SA
          Arista
        - Madame X - I want your body, 1987; SR-19704; Madame X (Box 344)
          Catalog # DMD 1123; A-side Matrix # ST-DM-53379-1
          12 inch
        - Madd Anju - Wat dis fada | Buddy she want, 1990; SR-19705; Madd Anju; Red Rat (Box 344)
          Catalog # VPRL6346; A-side Matrix # VPRD 6346 A
          VP Records
          Jamaica, New York
        - Madd Blunted - Rock it (rasta remix); Gettin high, 1995; SR-19706; Madd Blunted (Box 344)
          In same jacket as # SR-19707. 2 copies.
          Catalog # VR-1309; A-side Matrix # VR-1309-A
          Vision Records
        - Madd Blunted - Rock it (rasta remix); Gettin high, 1995; SR-19707; Madd Blunted (Box 344)
          In same jacket as # SR-19706. 2 copies.
        - Madd Nation - My senorita, 2000; SR-19708; Madd Nation (Box 344)
          Catalog # 101-A; A-side Matrix # "MY SENORITA" SIDE A
          Tone Struck Records
          Hollywood, California
        - Madd Rapper - DOT vs TMR (remix); Bongo breaks, 1999; SR-19709; Madd Rapper (Box 344)
          Catalog # CAS 46409; A-side Matrix # XSS-46409A-1A
        - Madd Rapper - You're all alone; DOT vs TMR, 1999; SR-19710; Madd Rapper (Box 344)
          Catalog # CAS 42521; A-side Matrix # XSS 42521 A-1
        - Madd Rapper - Selections from "tell em why u madd", 1999; SR-19711; Madd Rapper (Box 344)
          Catalog # CAS 42921; A-side Matrix # XSS-42921-A
        - Made Men - Is it you; Made men, 1998; SR-19712; Made Men (Box 344)
          Catalog # 0 1877 72995-1; A-side Matrix # 01877-72995-1A RE1
          Restless Records
        - Madhouse - Serve 'em, 1973; SR-19713; Madhouse (Box 344)
          Catalog # TLP-1010; A-side Matrix # TLP-1010-A
          Today Records
        - Madison Street - Hey look who's dancin', 1979; SR-19714; Madison Street (Box 344)
          Annotated.
          Catalog # INF 16,006; A-side Matrix # INF-16006-A-SS1
          Infinity Records
        - Mad Maxx - Hand me a mic, 2003; SR-19715; Mad Maxx (Box 344)
          Catalog # unknown; A-side Matrix # L-13722MA
          Blurred Insight Records
        - Madness - Our house, 1982; SR-19716; Madness (Box 344)
          In same jacket as # SR-19717. 2 copies. Annotated.
          Catalog # 0-29667; A-side Matrix # 0-29667-A-SH1
          Geffen Records
        - Madness - Our house, 1982; SR-19717; Madness (Box 344)
          In same jacket as # SR-19716. 2 copies.
        - Madonna - Gambler, 1985; SR-19718; Madonna (Box 344)
          Catalog # GEFA 12.6585; A-side Matrix # 01-126585-1A-1
        - Madonna - Everybody, 1982; SR-19719; Madonna (Box 344)
          In same jacket as # SR-19720. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 0-29899; A-side Matrix # 0-29899-A
          Burbank, California
        - Madonna - Everybody, 1982; SR-19720; Madonna (Box 344)
          In same jacket as # SR-19719. 2 copies.
        - Madonna - Papa don't preach, 1986; SR-19721; Madonna (Box 344)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2517; A-side Matrix # OB-24198-SH1
        - Madonna - Hanky panky, 1990; SR-19722; Madonna (Box 344)
          Catalog # 0-21577; A-side Matrix # 0-21577-A SR1
        - Madonna - Into the groove; Everybody, 1987; SR-19723; Madonna (Box 344)
          Catalog # PRO-A-1-2906; A-side Matrix # PRO-A-2906-SH-1
        - Madonna - You can dance, 1987; SR-19724; Madonna (Box 344)
          Catalog # 1-25535; A-side Matrix # 1 25535 A DMM SR1
        - Madonna - Angel, 1984; SR-19725; Madonna (Box 344)
          In same jacket as # SR-19726. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 0-20335; A-side Matrix # 0-20335-A-SR3
        - Madonna - Angel, 1984; SR-19726; Madonna (Box 344)
          In same jacket as # SR-19725. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 0-20335; A-side Matrix # 0-20335-A-SR1
        - Madonna - True blue, 1986; SR-19727; Madonna (Box 344)
          In same jacket as # SR-19728. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 1-25442; A-side Matrix # 1-25442ARE-1-SR-2
        - Madonna - True blue, 1986; SR-19728; Madonna (Box 344)
          In same jacket as # SR-19727. 2 copies.
          Catalog # 1-25442; A-side Matrix # 1-25442-A-RE-1
        - Madonna - True blue, 1986; SR-19729; Madonna (Box 344)
          Catalog # 0-20533; A-side Matrix # 0-20533A SH-1
        - Madonna - La isla bonita, 1987; SR-19730; Madonna (Box 344)
          Catalog # 0-20633; A-side Matrix # 0-20633-A-SH-1
        - Madonna - Justify my love, 1990; SR-19731; Madonna (Box 344)
          In same jacket as # SR-19732. Different discs.
          Catalog # 0-21820; A-side Matrix # 0-21820-A-SR1
        - Madonna - Justify my love, 1990; SR-19732; Madonna (Box 344)
          In same jacket as # SR-19731. Different discs.
          Catalog # PRO-A-4613; A-side Matrix # PRO-A1-4613-SR1
        - Madonna - American life (American dream remixes), 2003; SR-19733; Madonna; Elliot, Missy (Box 344)
          Catalog # PRO-A-101097; A-side Matrix # PRO A 101097-A
          Maverick
        - Madonna - Nothing really matters (disc one), 1998; SR-19734; Madonna (Box 344)
          In same jacket as # SR-19735. Double album.
          Catalog # PRO-A-9630; A-side Matrix # PRO A 9630-A SR1
        - Madonna - Nothing really matters (disc two), 1998; SR-19735; Madonna (Box 344)
          In same jacket as # SR-19734. Double album.
          Catalog # PRO-A-9630; A-side Matrix # PRO A 9630-C SR1
        - Madonna - Lucky star; Holiday, 1983; SR-19736; Madonna (Box 344)
          Catalog # PRO-A-2069; A-side Matrix # PRO A1 2069 SH1
        - Madstyle - Bloodrush, 1993; SR-19737; Madstyle (Box 345)
          Catalog # 55032; A-side Matrix # 55032-A
          Moonroof Records
        - Maestro - Death ministry; Puhsin' wiggz back, 1996; SR-19738; Maestro (Box 345)
          Catalog # MR0011; A-side Matrix # MAESTRO-A MR 0011A
          Maestro Records